Lish mss., 1951-2017 LMC 2404
Lilly Library
- X. Additions
  - Additional Correspondence (Box 133)
    - Person, Russell, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Quarnstrom, Lee, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Redel, Victoria, 2013 (Box 133)
    - Reisner, Alex, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Ross, Helen, 2014 (Box 133)
    - Rybicki, John, 2012 (Box 133)
    - Sampsell, Kevin, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Sarki, Michael, 2012 (Box 134)
    - Saunders, George, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Schwartz, Jason, 2012-2013, undated (Box 134)
    - Sklenicka, Carol, 2005 (Box 134)
    - Slutzky, Zöe, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Schreiner, Helen, 2012-2013 (Box 134)
    - Spohrer, Lauren, 2011 (Box 134)
    - Sparling, Ken, undated (Box 134)
    - Stark, Sam, 2012 (Box 134)
    - Sterritt, Brooks, 2012 (Box 134)
    - Sticker, Gerald, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Summell, Matt, 2012-2013 (Box 134)
    - Sussler, Betsy, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Tay, May-Lan, 2014, undated (Box 134)
    - Treanor, Tom, 2012 (Box 134)
    - Vasicek, René Georg, 2013 (Box 134)
    - Volk, Patty, 2012 (Box 134)
    - W. D., undated (Box 134)
    - Williams, Cherry, 2009 (Box 134)
    - Williams, Joy, 2014 (Box 134)
    - Yates, Mahala Stripling, 2012 (Box 134)
    - Zyzak, Magdalena, 2014, undated (Box 134)
    - Renner, Cooper, 2010-2014; (2 folders) (Box 134)
    - Ross, Helen Klein, 2013-2014 (Box 134)
    - Todd, Robb, 2012-2013 (Box 134)
    - Walsmith, Shelton, 2009-2014, undated (Box 134)
    - First name only, 2010-2014, undated (Box 134)
    - Unnamed, undated (Box 134)
  - Additional Writings
    - Anonymous Authors (Box 134)
      - Escalante (Box 134)
      - Virgin Queen (Box 134)
    - Cooperider, Carrie (Box 134)
      - On Those Days When We Are Present (Box 134)
      - Rivalry Among Males of the... (Box 134)
    - Evenson, Brian (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review) (Box 134)
    - Giles, Patrick (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review) (Box 134)
    - Glover, Douglas (Box 134)
      - Savage Love Stories (Box 134)
    - Hogan, Wayne H. (Box 134)
      - A Review of Research... (Box 134)
    - Jackson, Mitchell S. (Box 134)
      - The Residue Years (Box 134)
    - Kesey, Ken (Box 134)
      - A Celebration of Excellence (Box 134)
    - Kirkus Reviews (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review), May 15, 1998 (Box 134)
    - Kirkus Reviews (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review), Dec. 15, 1998 (Box 134)
    - Livingstone, David B. (Box 134)
      - Fiction that ignores the rules...(Review of Jason Schwartz) (Box 134)
    - Lutz, Gary (Box 134)
      - Partial List of People to Bleach (Box 134)
    - MH (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review) (Box 134)
    - Nutting, Alissa (Box 134)
    - Perachio, Cristina (Box 134)
    - Reynolds, Susan Salter (Box 134)
      - A German Picturesque (Review) (Box 134)
    - Schwartz, Jason (Box 134)
      - Account of a Drowning (Box 134)
      - Adulterium (Box 134)
      - At Hunt (Box 134)
      - A Brace of Grouse (Box 134)
      - Breviary (Box 134)
      - Division of the Field (Box 134)
      - The Dying Wives (Box 134)
      - The Fall Kill (Box 134)
      - The Form of Horses (Box 134)
      - Hornbook (Box 134)
      - Housepost, Male Figure (Box 134)
      - John the Posthumous (Box 134)
        - Bound, 2013 (Box 134)
        - Bound, Uncorrected Proofs (Box 135)
        - Unbound (Box 135)
      - A Map of Her Town (Box 135)
      - The Meaning of Steeples (Box 135)
      - Notation on Hidden Children (Box 135)
      - Notation on the Principal Graves (Box 135)
      - Rape in the Animal Kingdom (Box 135)
      - Rock Brake (Box 135)
      - Vestiary (Box 135)
      - Winter Register (Box 135)
      - Woodcut (Box 135)
    - Sticker, Gerald [Jerry] (Box 135)
      - You and Me and Superman (Box 135)
    - Tay, May-Lan (Box 135)
      - MBA Literary Agents LTD (Box 135)
      - Things to Make and Break (Box 135)
    - Unknown Author (Box 135)
      - Unknown Title (Box 135)
  - Additional Audio-Visual
    - Felderman, Irving (Box 135)
      - , Hammer Museum, Nov. 14, 2013 (Box 135)
    - IF 26 06 12, [Jun. 06, 2012] (Box 135)
      - CC2 (Box 135)
    - IF at ESC (Box 135)
    - Insignia Films, Trailer and Scenes (Box 135)
    - Lingus, Al (Box 135)
      - Blood of the Condor (Box 135)
      - St. Michael the Archangel (Box 135)
  - Additional Newspaper Clippings
    - 2014 (Box 135)
  - Additional Correspondence
    - Correspondence A-Fr (Box 135)
      - Andreou, George, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Baird, Ansie, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Bass, Rick, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Belden, Kathryn, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Blumberg, Ted, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Boyers, Bob, 2011-2013 (Box 136)
      - Buckley, Christopher, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Burton, Jane, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Charles, Norman, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Corman, Catherine Ann, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Coyne, Steve, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Eno, Will, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Fenimore, Carrie, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Flores, Paca(see Rodriguez, Julian), undated (Box 136)
      - Fogarty, B., 2015 (Box 136)
      - Frodenberg, Susan Gale Miller, 2015 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence Fu-G (Box 136)
      - Funke, Sarah, 2007 (Box 136)
      - Gangemi, Kenneth, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Gardner, Tom, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Gaylichwing, Pierre, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Geeslin, Campbell, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Gekiere, Madeleine, 2011 (Box 136)
      - Geronemus, Roy G., undated (Box 136)
      - Goebel, Luke B., 2014 (Box 136)
      - Groenland, Tim, 2015 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence H-K (Box 136)
      - Hamilton, Mary, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Hayward, Bill, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Hemmingson, Michael, 2008 (Box 136)
      - Hempel, Amy, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Henry, Casey Michael, undated (Box 136)
      - Hodges, John, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Hogan, Wayne, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Holland, Noy, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Horowitz, Glenn, 2007-2013 (Box 136)
      - Jiles, Paulette, undated (Box 136)
      - King, Susan, 2014 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence L (Box 136)
      - Lears, Jackson, 2013-2015 (Box 136)
      - Lebeaux, Michael, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Lee, J., 2015 (Box 136)
      - Lipsyte, Sam, 2013-2014 (Box 136)
      - Lish, Atticus, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Lish, Beth, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Livingstone, Carolyn, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Long, Daniel, undated (Box 136)
      - Lutz, Gary, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Lynch, Thomas, 2015 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence M-O (Box 136)
      - McCall, Bruce, undated (Box 136)
      - McKernan, John, undated (Box 136)
      - McNally, Rick, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Mahon, Eugene J., 2015 (Box 136)
      - Margetson, Evan, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Martin, Andy, undated (Box 136)
      - Millhauser, Anna, 2011 (Box 136)
      - Mulcahy, Greg, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Mutt, R., undated (Box 136)
      - Oakes, John, 2016 (Box 136)
      - O'Connell, Patricia, undated (Box 136)
      - Odell, Joshua S., 2014 (Box 136)
      - Ozick, Cynthia, 2011-2016 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence P-R (Box 136)
      - Persson, Russell, 2015-2016 (Box 136)
      - Raffel, Dawn, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Renner, Cooper, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Rodriguez, Julian, undated (Box 136)
      - Ross, Paul, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Rossmore, D., 2008-2011 (Box 136)
      - Ryder, Pamela, 2015 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence S-Z (Box 136)
      - Sarki, Michael, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
      - Schreiner, Helen E., 2015 (Box 136)
      - Schwartz, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Stanley, Morgan, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Stein, Lewis, undated (Box 136)
      - Sticker, Jerry, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Treanor, Tan, 2011 (Box 136)
      - Treska, Nicole, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Volmer, Stephanie, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Walsmith, Shelton, 2007-2014 (Box 136)
      - White, Derek, undated (Box 136)
      - Williams, Joy, 2015 (Box 136)
      - Winters, David, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
      - Wolitzer, Holma, 2014 (Box 136)
      - Zarela, O., 2010 (Box 136)
      - Zyzak, Magdalena, 2013 (Box 136)
    - From Lish, 2014-2015 (Box 136)
    - First name only, 1984-2016 (Box 136)
    - Unidentified, 2014-2016 (Box 136)
  - Additional Writings by Others
    - Writings by Others D (Box 136)
      - DeLillo, Don (Box 136)
    - Writings by Others H-K (Box 136)
      - Hogan, Wayne (Box 136)
      - Holland, Noy (Box 136)
      - Konrad, Evelyn (Box 136)
    - Writings by Others Mc (Box 136)
      - McNally, Rick (Box 136)
    - Writings by Others M (Box 136)
      - Margetson, Evan K. (Box 136)
    - Writings R-Z (Box 136)
      - Ryder, Pamela (Box 136)
      - Treska, Nicole (Box 136)
      - Zukerman, Alexandra (Box 136)
  - Additional Writings
    - "Death and Language" (Box 136)
    - Unidentified (Box 136)
  - Additional Photographs
    - Albertine (Box 136)
    - Jim and Liz (Box 136)
    - Walsmith, Shelton (Box 136)
  - Additional A/V
    - "You Know my Name, You Know Where I Live", 2015 (Box 136)
  - Additional Miscellaneous
    - Restricted (grades) (Box 136)
  - Additional Clippings
    - Press on Lish, 1960-2017 (Box 136)
      - Folders 1-12 (Box 137)
      - Folders 13-24 (Box 138)
      - Folders 25-37 (Box 139)
      - Folders 38-49 (Box 140)
      - Folders 50-54 (Box 141)
      - Oversize magazines and magazines relating to Lish (Box 142)
  - Additional Correspondence
    - A-B, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Burton, Jane, 2015-2017 (Box 141)
    - C-G, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Hogan, Wayne, 2015-2017 (Box 141)
    - Jilesjohnson, Paulette, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - K-L, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Latimer, Andrew, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - M-P, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Persson, Russell, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Q-R, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Raritan, 2016 (Box 141)
    - Renner, Cooper, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - S-Z, 2016-2017 (Box 141)
    - Unidentified, 2015-2017 (Box 141)
  - Additional Writings by Other Authors
    - Coyne, Stephen, 2016 (Box 141)
    - Lear, Patricia, 2016 (Box 141)
    - Persson, Russell, 2016 (Box 141)
    - Ryder, Pamela, 2016 (Box 141)
    - Topp, Mike, 2016 (Box 141)
  - Additional Photographs
    - Lish and Raymond Carver, 1980s? (Box 141)